[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_052",
        "question": "A healthy 12-month-old infant girl presents with a yellowish-orange papule on the right upper extremity. <br>- Her mother first noticed this lesion approximately 6 months earlier. <br>- It has never bled, ulcerated, or formed blisters. <br>- The infant does not scratch the lesion nor appears otherwise bothered by it. <br>- However, when the lesion is rubbed, it appears to swell and turn bright red. <br>- On physical examination, there is a soft, oval-shaped, yellowish papule with a peripheral rim of erythema on the right extensor forearm.",
        "option1": "Solitary mastocytoma",
        "option2": "Epidermolysis bullosa",
        "option3": "Bullous arthropod bites",
        "option4": "Pseudomonas nail infection",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "87%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_104",
        "question": "An 8-year-old male presents with 1 week of itchy blisters on the ears. <br>- He just recently returned from spring break with his family. <br>- He denies using any particular products on the ears before the rash. <br>- He says that this has occurred yearly for the last several years, always around the same time. <br>- He denies proximal muscle weakness. <br>- He denies flaking in the scalp. <br>- Physical examination reveals tiny vesicles atop erythematous patches on the superior helices.",
        "option1": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "option2": "Juvenile dermatomyositis",
        "option3": "Juvenile spring eruption",
        "option4": "Allergic contact dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_105",
        "question": "A 67-year-old male presents with unrelenting itch present over the last 6 months. <br>- He endorses weight loss and fatigue. <br>- He denies any liver or kidney disease. <br>- He denies exacerbation of itch with water. <br>- A KOH scraping is performed which is negative for scabies. <br>- Physical examination is significant for numerous punctate and linear erosions consistent with excoriations as well as diffuse shoddy lymphadenopathy.",
        "option1": "Scabies",
        "option2": "Renal pruritus",
        "option3": "Cholestatic pruritus",
        "option4": "Hodgkin lymphoma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_047",
        "question": "A 13-year-old girl presents with a cystic lesion that has been on her forearm for several years. <br>- Concerned about the lesion, she reports that it may have grown slightly larger in the past year and it is intermittently painful. <br>- More recently, a second similar lesion has appeared in close proximity. <br>- She denies any other suspicious lesions elsewhere on her skin. <br>- Her family history is negative for skin cancer, and she reports no other medical conditions. <br>- Physical examination reveals two well-defined 6-mm nodules that are rubbery, slightly tender, and pink on the right proximal ventral forearm. <br>- The overlying skin is intact, and there is no associated adenopathy.",
        "option1": "Angiolipoma",
        "option2": "Spiradenoma",
        "option3": "Glomus tumor",
        "option4": "neuroma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_068",
        "question": "A 4-year-old white male presents with a 3-month history of an asymptomatic papular rash on his back, abdomen, chest, upper arms, and ankles. <br>- His medical and family histories are otherwise unremarkable. <br>- On examination, the grouped papules are shiny, monomorphic, skin-colored, and pinhead-sized. <br>- The papules exhibit koebnerization but no erythema or tenderness. <br>- His nails, hair, oral mucosa, and genitals are normal.",
        "option1": "Lichen striatus",
        "option2": "Lichen planus",
        "option3": "Guttate lichen sclerosus",
        "option4": "Lichen nitidus",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "41%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_054",
        "question": "A 43-year-old elementary school teacher presents with a rash that began on his left thigh approximately 4 months earlier; the rash has since spread. <br>- It is mildly itchy but has no associated pain or bleeding. <br>- His past medical history is significant for allergic rhinitis and atopic dermatitis. <br>- Suspecting eczema, he has been applying an over-the-counter hydrocortisone 1% cream as well as a moisturizer, which transiently alleviates the itch. <br>- He has not changed laundry or hygiene products. <br>- On physical examination, there are slightly erythematous, minimally scaly patches scattered over his left hip and buttock.",
        "option1": "Eczema",
        "option2": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "option3": "Tinea incognito",
        "option4": "Cutaneous lupus",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_025",
        "question": "An 8-year-old African-American boy presents with a 3-day history of fever, pain, and a rash on his trunk. <br>- On examination, the patient has several fragile, bullous lesions on his trunk, many of which have eroded, exposing erythematous, annular lesions. <br>- The patient is febrile and shaking in the office, and he appears to be in pain. <br>- He has no other relevant social or family history and does not take any medications. <br>- His mother is very concerned about her son.",
        "option1": "Stevens-Johnson syndrome",
        "option2": "Autoimmune bullous dermatoses",
        "option3": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option4": "Bullous erythema multiforme",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_055",
        "question": "A 50-year-old woman presents with a 5-day history of progressive, painful rash involving her face, trunk, extremities, nasal tip, and ears, in addition to fever and arthralgia. <br>- She admits to a history of polysubstance use and states that her last use was a week prior to symptom onset. <br>- She denies a history of autoimmune disease or recent travel. <br>- Examination reveals retiform purpura with areas of necrosis and bullae formation. <br>- Urine toxicology screening is positive for cocaine, and laboratory findings include leukopenia and an elevated erythrocyte sedimentation rate (70 mm/h).",
        "option1": "Tinea incognito",
        "option2": "Levamisole-induced antineutrophil cytoplasmic antibody vasculitis",
        "option3": "Disseminated intravascular coagulation",
        "option4": "Warfarin-induced skin necrosis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_071",
        "question": "A 61-year-old woman presents with a 7-month history of a bump on the front of her left knee. <br>- The lesion is slightly tender but otherwise is asymptomatic. <br>- She is concerned that the lesion may be cancerous. <br>- She has no other medical problems and takes vitamin D daily. <br>- On physical examination, a firm subcutaneous tumor is noted on the left knee measuring 8 cm without overlying skin changes. <br>- She has no other similar lesions elsewhere on her body.",
        "option1": "Ganglion cyst",
        "option2": "Lipoma",
        "option3": "Synovial cyst",
        "option4": "Pigmented villonodular synovitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "86%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_018",
        "question": "A 38-year-old African American woman was referred to dermatology because of spots on her torso and arms. <br>- The lesions were asymptomatic, but their development, cause, and cosmesis were of concern. <br>- No benefit was seen with the use of OTC remedies such as hydroxycortisone 1% cream or vitamin E oil. <br>- Her medical history was significant for systemic lupus erythematosus, well controlled on hydroxychloroquine. <br>- Physical examination revealed numerous, well-circumscribed, 0.5- to 2-cm, hypopigmented, round-to-oval macules of wrinkled skin on her anterior chest wall, back, abdomen, and bilateral upper arms. <br>- Invagination of the lesions was noted with palpation. <br>- A punch biopsy was performed.",
        "option1": "Anetoderma associated with SLE",
        "option2": "Cutis laxa",
        "option3": "Post-inflammatory elastolysis",
        "option4": "Mid-dermal elastolysis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "94%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_100",
        "question": "A 54-year-old woman presents with 2 years of gradual hair thinning. <br>- She says that her mother also experienced hair thinning starting in her 50s. <br>- She denies scalp itch. <br>- She denies clumps of hair coming out in the shower or on her pillow. <br>- She denies any preceding stressful life events. <br>- She denies wearing her hair in tight braids. <br>- She denies loss of eyebrows or eyelashes. <br>- Physical examination reveals frontotemporal hair thinning without scarring.",
        "option1": "Central centrifugal cicatricial alopecia",
        "option2": "Telogen effluvium",
        "option3": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option4": "Alopecia areata",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "55%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_136",
        "question": "A 65-year-old female presents to the dermatology clinic for evaluation of eyelid redness and neck rash ongoing for four months that began after she started a new body lotion. <br>- She reports increasing fatigue when climbing stairs and lifting heavy items over her head. <br>- She has not tried any topical treatments. <br>- She denies any recent medication changes, fevers, chills, or recent travel. <br>-   Physical examination reveals poorly demarcated patchy pink erythema affecting the periocular areas with a bright pink poorly demarcated patch diffusely across the upper back and shoulders in the shape of a V. <br>- The bilateral dorsal hands reveals thin pink rough plaques on the knuckle joints.",
        "option1": "Allergic contact dermatitis",
        "option2": "Rheumatoid arthritis",
        "option3": "Lupus erythematosus",
        "option4": "Dermatomyositis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_099",
        "question": "An 8-year-old boy presents to the clinic for evaluation of a progressively worsening nail dystrophy that began a few months ago. <br>- The patient’s mother denies a family history of skin diseases and reports that her son has no history of medical problems. <br>- On physical examination, all of the boy’s fingernails and toenails show hyperkeratosis, longitudinal ridging, loss of luster, and roughness. <br>- His hair, skin, and oral mucosa are unremarkable. <br>- Nail biopsy reveals spongiotic changes and exocytosis of inflammatory cells into the nail epithelia. <br>- The results of a fungal culture are negative.",
        "option1": "Brittle nails",
        "option2": "Trachyonychia",
        "option3": "Onychomycosis",
        "option4": "Senile nails",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "52%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_013",
        "question": "A 24-year-old Caucasian woman presented with intermittent, inflammatory papulopustules and nodules on the face, neck, chest, and back. <br>- The lesions would appear 1 week premenstrually and resolve 1 week postmenstrually with normal menstrual cycles. <br>- She has a history of adolescent acne that is only responsive to isotretinoin 6 years ago. <br>- Examination revealed scarring and postinflammatory hyperpigmentation diffusely on her face.",
        "option1": "Rosacea",
        "option2": "Acne vulgaris",
        "option3": "Alopecia",
        "option4": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_129",
        "question": "A 66-year-old woman with a past medical history of hypertension and diabetes mellitus type 2 presents to clinic with a mildly painful, pruritic peeling skin on the chest and back that began 4 weeks ago. <br>- She denies any new medications, new topical creams or lotions, or laundry detergents. <br>- She has been applying vaseline to the spots. <br>- She also thinks she may have a similar spot on the scalp. <br>- She denies any similar spots in the mouth, and denies forming any blisters on the skin. <br>-   Physical exam demonstrates multiple thinly eroded pink-red oval plaques on the chest, scalp, back with yellow brown corn-flake like scale. <br>- Ocular and oral mucosa are normal.",
        "option1": "Pemphigus vulgaris",
        "option2": "Bullous arthropod assault",
        "option3": "Bullous pemphigoid",
        "option4": "Pemphigus foliaceous",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "49%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]